<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Info description="This Simulink Project contains Simulink I/O integration layer with control system and ground station model for RRTV. This is intended to be used with PX4 Autopilot.&#xa;&#xa;Github sources:&#xa;https://github.com/YevheniiKovryzhenko/RRTV_TiltWing.git&#xa;https://github.com/YevheniiKovryzhenko/PX4_SIMULINK_IO_Framework.git&#xa;&#xa;% /****************************************************************************&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  *    Copyright (C) 2024  Yevhenii Kovryzhenko. All rights reserved.&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  *    This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify&#xa;%  *    it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as published by&#xa;%  *    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or&#xa;%  *    (at your option) any later version.&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  *    This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,&#xa;%  *    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of&#xa;%  *    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the&#xa;%  *    GNU Affero General Public License Version 3 for more details.&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  *    You should have received a copy of the&#xa;%  *    GNU Affero General Public License Version 3&#xa;%  *    along with this program.  If not, see &lt;https://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  *    1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright&#xa;%  *       notice, this list of conditions, and the following disclaimer.&#xa;%  *    2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright&#xa;%  *       notice, this list of conditions, and the following disclaimer in&#xa;%  *       the documentation and/or other materials provided with the&#xa;%  *       distribution.&#xa;%  *    3. No ownership or credit shall be claimed by anyone not mentioned in&#xa;%  *       the above copyright statement.&#xa;%  *    4. Any redistribution or public use of this software, in whole or in part,&#xa;%  *       whether standalone or as part of a different project, must remain&#xa;%  *       under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License Version 3,&#xa;%  *       and all distributions in binary form must be accompanied by a copy of&#xa;%  *       the source code, as stated in the GNU Affero General Public License.&#xa;%  *&#xa;%  ****************************************************************************/"/>